http://www.thefocalpoint.com/privacy-policy

AboutTeamProcessValuesCareers ServicesPersuasion StrategyExpert WitnessJury ConsultingOnline ResearchTrial GraphicsTrial PresentationTrialLink InsightsCOVID-19BooksCLEArticlesDesign Thinking
Clients CasesClass ActionCommercialConstructionCriminalEmploymentEnvironmentalInsuranceIPITCSecurities Contact
Privacy Policy
HomePrivacy Policy
Intelligent Management Solutions, LLC d/b/a IMS|The Focal Point is committed to the privacy of the users of its website (the "Site"). We created this policy to give you confidence as you use the Site and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and the protection of privacy. This policy only applies to the Site and not to any other website maintained by any other person.
In operating the Site, we may include registration, and other online forms that ask users to provide their names, e-mail addresses, and other contact information. Otherwise, we do not collect personal information or individually identifying information from any user, other than user names and passwords for private client websites. We may disclose information collected by us if required to do so by law or to comply with legal process or, under exigent circumstances, to protect the safety of the public or users of the Site. Otherwise, we do not share any information collected by us with any other person.
We do not use cookies. We do not link to other websites. Users do not provide any content to the Site. We do not direct any of our content to children under 13 years of age, and if we learn that a Site user is under age 13, we will promptly delete any personal information we may have collected from that user.
While we do not maintain any procedures for you to review or request changes to any personal information about you, you may request at any time that we remove all information about you from our database (if any) by contacting us at the following email address: info@thefocalpoint.com
We reserve the right at any time to add to, change, update, or modify this Policy, simply by posting any change, update, or modification on the Site, and without any other notice to you. Any change, update or modification shall be effective upon posting to the Site. This Privacy Policy is effective October 1, 2005.
We provide a custom and efficient approach to work within your budget.
Contact us 877. 752. 1760
DALLAS
NEW YORK
OAKLAND
Site Map    |
Terms of Use    |
Privacy Policy    |
Careers
© 2020 Intelligent Management Solutions, LLC. The Focal Point® and Mental Mining® are federally registered service marks of Intelligent Management Solutions, LLC.
